Guide to the H. G. Merriam Papers 1890-1980
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photographs, 1914-1975; Series XII; 2.25 linear feet
  - Hal Dietemann and Ted Waddell demonstrating to Baby Morrtgomen and others the process of centrifugal casting, undated; 487(XII):196 (Box-folder 39/46)
  - Ethel Ann Edwards of Lewiston among craft exhibit, undated; 487(XII):197 (Box-folder 39/47)
  - Ethel Ann Edwards of Lewiston, examining Mae Lewis's sculpture foreground shapes by Kay Smith, Butte, undated; 487(XII):198 (Box-folder 39/48)
  - Festival director and his sister, Mrs. Al Leidie of Billings, looking over Mai Lewis's "The Frontier Family", undated; 487(XII):199 (Box-folder 39/49)
  - Group of Billings people examining pottery exhibit, undated; 487(XII):200 (Box-folder 39/50)
  - Frolie in Black and white by Manker, undated; 487(XII):201 (Box-folder 39/51)
  - August by Leia Anfie, undated; 487(XII):202 (Box-folder 39/52)
  - Picture of Joseph Kinsey Howard, undated; 487(XII):203 (Box-folder 39/53)
  - Studio of Charlie Russell during his professional painting days, undated; 487(XII):204 (Box-folder 39/54)
  - C.M. Russell gallery, Great Falls, undated; 487(XII):205 (Box-folder 39/55)
  - Map of little festival showings (Montana), 1954-1955, 1957-1958; 487(XII):206 (Box-folder 39/56)
  - Wearings at the 7th annual festival, 1955; 487(XII):207 (Box-folder 39/57)
  - Charcoal drawing by James M. Haughey, 1958; 487(XII):208 (Box-folder 39/58)
  - Exhibits in the 1960 festival, undated; 487(XII):209 (Box-folder 39/59)
  - Horse drawing by Gilberta Manker, 1961; 487(XII):210 (Box-folder 39/60)
  - Metal Buffalo sculpture by Lyndon Pomeroy, undated; 487(XII):211 (Box-folder 39/61)
  - Drawings by James E. Dew, 1963; 487(XII):212 (Box-folder 39/62)
  - Peter Voulkos throwing a pot, 1964; 487(XII):213 (Box-folder 39/63)
  - Exhibits at the 1966 festival, 487(XII):214 (Box-folder 39/64)
  - Paintings Combine XXIX by Charles Daugherty, 1968; 487(XII):215 (Box-folder 39/65)
  - Painting working herd by J.K. Ralston, 1969; 487(XII):216 (Box-folder 39/66)
  - Gallery Talk by Raymond Campeau, 1972 festival, 487(XII):217 (Box-folder 39/67)
  - Silk screens from her African Series by Jessie Wilber, 1972; 487(XII):218 (Box-folder 39/68)
  - Painting The Pit by Raymond Cambeau, 1972; 487(XII):219 (Box-folder 39/69)
  - Magazine cover by Jessie Wilber, 1974; 487(XII):220 (Box-folder 39/70)
  - Sculpture Edmonton Trader by Jack Weaver, 1975; 487(XII):221 (Box-folder 39/71)
  - Marketplace at 1975 festival, Virginia and E.H. Loeffler, 487(XII):222 (Box-folder 39/72)
  - Blown glass by David Cornell, 1976; 487(XII):223 (Box-folder 39/73)
  - Magazine cover by Lyndon Pomeroy, Fall 1953; 487(XII):224 (Box-folder 39/74)
  - The Taxation of mines in Montana by Louis Levine, Ph. D. Book Cover, undated; 487(XII):225 (Box-folder 39/75)
  - The Frontier A magazine of the Northwest, cover, 1933 March; 487(XII):226 (Box-folder 39/76)
  - University of Montana--Missoula Campus, (ca. 1900); 487(XII):227 (Box-folder 39/77)
  - Unidentified man, undated; 487(XII):228 (Box-folder 39/78)
  - Edward C. Elliot, Chancellor of the Montana University System from 1916 thru 1922, undated; 487(XII):229 (Box-folder 39/79)
  - Lewis Orvis Evans, undated; 487(XII):230 (Box-folder 39/80)
  - Man in front of building, undated; 487(XII):231 (Box-folder 39/81)
  - Empty room with sunlight shining through window, undated; 487(XII):232 (Box-folder 39/82)
  - H. G. Merriam, 1930; 487(XII):233 (Box-folder 39/83)
  - H. G. Merriam, 1939; 487(XII):234 (Box-folder 39/84)
  - H. G. Merriam and group, 1952; 487(XII):235 (Box-folder 39/85)
  - H. G. Merriam and group, 1954; 487(XII):236 (Box-folder 39/86)
  - H. G. Merriam and Dr. Harold Urey, undated; 487(XII):237 (Box-folder 39/87)
  - H. G. Merriam and another before ceremony, 1979; 487(XII):238 (Box-folder 39/88)
  - H. G. Merriam-multiple shots, contact negatives, undated; 487(XII):239 (Box-folder 39/89)
  - Museum of the Plains Indian, Frank Bird Linderman exhibit, 1962; 487(XII):240 (Box-folder 39/90)
  - Museum of the Plains Indian, Norman Linderman Waller, 1962; 487(XII):241 (Box-folder 39/91)
  - Mrs. E. Douglas Branch, 1942; 487(XII):242 (Box-folder 39/92)
  - H.L. Davis, Portal, AZ, 1930; 487(XII):243 (Box-folder 39/93)
  - Mary Ronan, undated; 487(XII):244 (Box-folder 39/94)
  - Paul W. Anderson and friends of Merriam ("Herron" on far left), 1939; 487(XII):245 (Box-folder 39/95)
  - Clare Aven Thomson, South Seas with turtle, undated; 487(XII):246 (Box-folder 39/96)
  - Care Aven Thomson, South Seas with sail fish, undated; 487(XII):247 (Box-folder 39/96)
  - Badger Clarke, undated; 487(XII):248 (Box-folder 39/97)
  - Man at pottery wheel (negative), undated; 487(XII):249 (Box-folder 39/98)
  - Portrait (negatives), undated; 487(XII):250 (Box-folder 39/99)
  - Group of people, undated; 487(XII):172 (Box Negs. box)
  - H. G. Merriam, New York, 1939; 487(XII):234 (Box Negs. box)
  - H. G. Merriam, 1973; 487(XII):239 (Box Negs. box)
  - H. G. Merriam, 1973; 487(XII):239 (Box Negs. box)
  - Farm house, undated; 487(XII):243 (Box Negs. box)
  - Unidentified man, undated; 487(XII):244 (Box Negs. box)
  - Visitors at art exhibit, undated; 487(XII):245 (Box Negs. box)
  - H. G. Merriam, undated; 487(XII):246 (Box Negs. box)